http://www.accesscm.co.uk/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Skip to content
Select LanguageEnglishAfrikaansAlbanianAmharicArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBengaliBosnianBulgarianCatalanCebuanoChichewaChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CorsicanCroatianCzechDanishDutchEsperantoEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchFrisianGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekGujaratiHaitian CreoleHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIcelandicIgboIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseJavaneseKannadaKazakhKhmerKoreanKurdish (Kurmanji)KyrgyzLaoLatinLatvianLithuanianLuxembourgishMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalteseMaoriMarathiMongolianMyanmar (Burmese)NepaliNorwegianPashtoPersianPolishPortuguesePunjabiRomanianRussianSamoanScottish GaelicSerbianSesothoShonaSindhiSinhalaSlovakSlovenianSomaliSpanishSudaneseSwahiliSwedishTajikTamilTeluguThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduUzbekVietnameseWelshXhosaYiddishYorubaZulu
Access Credit Management
About UsOur HistoryCompany InformationServicesInternational Debt CollectionUK Commercial Debt RecoveryInformationBusiness FinanceCredit ManagementInsolvency OptionsOutsourced Credit ControlTrade Credit InsuranceContactFAQsLinks & Resources
Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy describes our collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information. Please read it carefully as this notice applies to any website, application or service which refers to our website Privacy Policy.
The Privacy Policy applies to all products and services available via Access Credit Management Limited’s website, http://www.accesscm.co.uk/, such as commercial debt recovery, international debt collection, applying for a vacancy or submitting an enquiry.
1. Who are we?
Access Credit Management Limited is a Commercial Credit Management company based in Sheffield, South Yorkshire. We specialise in Commercial Debt Recovery, Global Commercial Debt Collection, Commercial Credit Management Reviews and Advice in the Commercial Credit Management Arena.
The registered address is Suites G1 & G3, Epic House, 18 Darnall Road, Sheffield, S9 5AA, United Kingdom.
2. How we collect information
When you use our website, you are in control of what information is collected. We only collect relevant personal information about you, and any other individual whose details you provide to us.
We’ll collect this when you:
Submit an enquiry for Commercial Debt Collection
Submit an enquiry for Global Commercial Debt Recovery.
Chat to our online operatives.
2b. What information do we collect?
Information about your computer and about your visits to, and use of, the website (including your IP address, approximate geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views); we will ask for your permission before we do so. We may do this using cookies or similar technologies.
This may include your name, business name, telephone number, email address, postal address or delegate names.
2c. How is your information used?
We will use your information to:
Contact you to arrange a meeting or provide a quote
Send you communications which you have requested
-this may include information about specific areas of our services which you have shown an interest in.
We’ll only contact you in relation to your original query.
Your information may also be used by Access Credit Management Limited to generate website user reports, this is analytical information and does not include your personal data.
We’ll only store this data for a period of 3 years, at which point it will be removed from our company server.
2d. Who has access to your information?
We do not sell or rent your information to third parties and your information will not be shared for marketing purposes.
3. Your choice
We will not contact you for marketing purposes by email, post, phone or text unless you have given your prior consent.
You can contact us at any time to request the information we have in relation to your personal data. If you would like us to remove/destroy any personal data we hold on you, you can contact us by emailing: legal@accesscm.co.uk or call + 44 (0)114 2499970 where your request will be given due consideration in line with current GDPR legislation.
4. Using cookies or other on-device storage
Cookies are information files stored on your computer, tablet or smartphone that help websites remember who you are and information about your visit. For further information (including how to opt out of cookies) please go to the Cookie Policy.
5. Tracking how the website is used
Information may be collected about activity on the website, or other organisations may be used to collect it and to share it. This information is used to:
analyse statistics;
track pages and paths used by visitors to, or users of, the website;
target the adverts or offers, such as banners, on the website and on the websites of other organisations; and
track the use of the internet banner adverts and other links from marketing partners' websites to this website.
For these purposes, the information on the path you take to get to the website and on some of the pages you visit or use through the website, using cookies, web beacons and other on-device storage will be retained. For information about web beacons, or the organisation used (including how to decline their cookies), please go to the Cookie Policy.
6. How your information is kept secure
The security of information is taken very seriously. Technology and security policies are in place to protect the information held.
7. Links to other websites
Our website includes links to other websites run by other organisations as a source of further information. This privacy statement only refers to this website, www.accesscm.co.uk, and we would encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites you visit.
We cannot be held responsible for privacy policies on third party sites linked from our site.
8. How changes to this privacy policy may occur
This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you may want to check it each time you visit the website. This policy was last updated May 2018.
9. Requesting Data
Through GDPR you have the right to request what data we are holding on you. To do this, please formalise your request through writing and posting a letter to Access Credit Management Limited’s head office at the following address:
DPO Officer
Access Credit Management Limited
Suites G1 & G3,
Epic House
18 Darnall Road
Sheffield
United Kingdom
10. Copyright
Entire Contents. All rights reserved.
All copyright, trademarks and all other intellectual property rights in the Website and its content (including without limitation the Website design, text, graphics and all software and source codes connected with the Website) are owned by or licensed to Access Credit Management Limited or otherwise used by Access Credit Management Limited as permitted by law.
In accessing the Website you agree that you will access the content solely for your personal, non-commercial use. None of the content may be downloaded, copied, reproduced, transmitted, stored, sold or distributed without the prior written consent of the copyright holder. This excludes the downloading, copying and/or printing of pages of the Website for personal, non-commercial home use only.
11. Disclaimer
The material on our site is given for general information only and does not constitute professional advice. You should take specific advice before taking a course of action as we do not accept directly or indirectly any responsibility for loss arising directly or indirectly from reliance on information on this site.
Given that the Internet uses an open system we cannot warrant that the site and downloads reach you virus-free. You must, therefore, take all appropriate precautions for your own safety.
12. Changes To Website
Access Credit Management Limited reserves the right to:
change or remove (temporarily or permanently) the Website or any part of it without notice and you confirm that Access Credit Management shall not be liable to you for any such change or removal; and change these Terms and Conditions at any time, and your continued use of the Website following any changes shall be deemed to be your acceptance of such change.
Get in Touch
Call Us: +44(0)207 305 5059
Request a Quote
Important Notice
Access Credit Management Limited will not accept any debt for recovery purposes, which has been authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority for accounts formed under the Consumer Credit Act 1974 (amended 2006)
Licensed by the Data Protection Act 1984.
ACM carries Professional Indemnity Cover for the security of client funds and client peace of mind.
An 'A' Credit Worthy Rated Company
ACM, established in March 2000, continues to be rated as a credit worthy business by leading providers of commercial credit information and is a member of the International Association of Credit and Collection Professionals.
Trade with Confidence
Our objective is to simply assist our clients to trade with confidence with existing and future clients on a national and international level and our continued success has been built upon providing a service that meets with client requirements.
Fully Licensed
The company is fully compliant in respect of its credit collection protocols. Access Credit Management Limited specialise in Commercial and International Debt Recovery.
Access Credit Management,
Suites G1, 18 Darnall Road,
Sheffield,
South Yorkshire,
S9 5AA,
United Kingdom
https://www.accesscm.co.uk/sites/default/files/access-credit-management-...
Customer Service:
London:
+44(0)207 305 5059
Customer Service:
Head Office:
+44 (0)114 24 999 70
Customer Service:
UK Free Phone:
+44 (0)800 694 0484
Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy | Terms & Conditions | Terms & Conditions of Business | Site Map
© 2020. Website Design by Introspective, Sheffield. All Rights Reserved.
